

Brian Freedman

UI and UX Expert

ABOUT ME

I have over 10 years of experience designing for the web, and I specialize in UI design, UX visual design, product design, design. information architecture, branding, design process management and prototyping. I have served varied verticals in my career and I have developed sound knowledge of user behavior and responsiveness.

CONTACT ME

+41 (0) 22 950 14 78



mail@briangeneva.com www.briangeneva.com.



Main Street, Ruy Geneva, Suisse

CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA

Facebook

facebook.com/brianfreed

Behance

BrianFreedma

brianfree

ANGUAGE

Spanish

Italian

EXPERTISE

Design Thinking =

Design Strategy

UX Design 1

UI Design . Usability Evaluation Creative Branding .

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

UI and UX Manager MindSpark Creative Agency

resent

Designed and Developed UI and UX for flagship products of MindSpark. Guided the team to deliver the UX design for the SAC products

Principal UX Consultant Sim6 Corporation

2008 - 2011

Redesigned the UI of major softwares of Sim6 Corporation. Collaborated with the global interactive team to build capabilities and deliver UX projects.

Media Designer Luecent Techno Media

2006 - 2008

Designed UI and UX of major applications and softwares. Executed several projects and managed design team. Worked towards establishing a design competence center.

RPROJECTS

Brand Development for Videocon

Designed complete brand identity for the Indian electronics company Videocoo. Re-designed the UI of their website.

UI and UX Design for Plex

Revamped the UI for the popular mobile application Plex. Designed the advertisement strategy for the client and developed ads.

UI, UX and Identity Development for Teradata

Overhauled the front-end UI and UX of the Teradata website and softwares. Designed the web-front for users and developed identity collateral.

EDUCATION

Masters in Product Design

2004 - 2006

Major in design arts.

Faculte Des Lettres, University of Geneva.

Bachelors in Design

2002 - 2004

Major in graphic design.

Faculte Des Lettres, University of Geneva.

Diploma in Calligraphy

2004 - 2004

Undertook an 8 month long course in Calligraphy and the art of lettering.

REFERENCE

Mrs. Caroline Goretta

Project Director MindSpark Creative Agency +41-(0)-22379-78 mindspark.com

Mr. Hany Glerum

Director Sim6 Corporation +41-(0)-82571-13 sim6systems.com